Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Audio Cassette Tapes: Meetings, Bulk, 1978-1989; 1966 - 1999
  - Subseries III:A: National
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Dec 13, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2326)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Dec 13, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2327)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Includes Si Gerson, Pat Barile, Jarvis Tyner, Carole Collier. Tape 3, Dec 13, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2328)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 13, Dec 14, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2332)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary. Tape 14, Dec 14, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2333)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Charlene Mitchell, On Wilmington 10 Victory. James Jackson, on Events in Poland, Dec 14, 1980 (Box 43, Cassette 3136)
    - Central Committee Meeting / Daily World Forum. James Jackson, Events in Poland. New York, NY, Dec 14, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2334)
    - Central Committee Meeting / Daily World Forum. James Jackson, Events in Poland. New York, NY, Dec 14, 1980 (Box 40, Cassette 2336)
    - Central Committee Meeting. [Henry Winston (?)] Speech on Executive Leadership., Jan 17, 1981 (Box 36, Cassette 1110)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 1, Jun 13, 1981-Jun 14, 1981 (Box 45, Cassette 1897)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Sid Taylor, Special Report on Membership Drive. Unity Center, New York, NY, Jun 14, 1981 (Box 40, Cassette 2339)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report, Jun 18, 1981 (Box 40, Cassette 2340)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary., Jun 18, 1981 (Box 40, Cassette 2320)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Education, Dec 1981 (Box 40, Cassette 2342)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Educational on Electoral Policy, Struggle for Peace and Building the Party, Dec 1981 (Box 45, Cassette 1873)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Educational on Electoral Policy, Struggle for Peace and Building the Party, Dec 1981 (Box 45, Cassette 1922)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Educational on Electoral Policy, Struggle for Peace and Building the Party, Dec 1981 (Box 40, Cassette 2344)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Dec 1981 (Box 42, Cassette 2687)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Dec 1981 (Box 42, Cassette 2702)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Dec 1981 (Box 42, Cassette 2686)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, Report on W.M.R. Conference in Berlin, Dec 14, 1981 (Box 36, Cassette 976)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 2, [Oct 29, 1982] (Box 40, Cassette 2341)
    - [Central Committee Meetings], 1982, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2319)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 1, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 39, Cassette 1998)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 1, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 42, Cassette 2700)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 2, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 39, Cassette 1999)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 2, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 42, Cassette 2701)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Tape 1, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2353)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Tape 2, Jan 29, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2354)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Tape 2 (incomplete), Jan 29, 1983 (Box 45, Cassette 1900)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, Jan 31, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2352)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Opening Plenum, Tape 2, May 28, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2348)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall and George Meyers, May 28, 1983-May 30, 1983 (Box 42, Cassette 2753)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, May 30, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2349)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, May 30, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2350)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, May 30, 1983 (Box 40, Cassette 2351)
    - Central Committee Meeting, Jan 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2355)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Si Gerson, Report, Jan 20, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2356)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Remarks on Electoral Report, Jan 21, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2734)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston. Tape 5, Jan 21, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2357)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Report, Jan 22, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2358)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, Jan 22, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2737)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall on Leadership, Jan 23, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1888)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Jun 16, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1996)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Jun 16, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 1995)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Conclusion. Tape 5, Jun 17, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1896)
    - Central Committee / National Council Meeting. George Myers, James Jackson and Henry Winston, Jun 17, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1866)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1894)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2016)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2731)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1891)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2014)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2745)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1883)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary. Tape 3, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2015)
    - Central Committee Meeting. James Jackson. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2359)
    - Central Committee Meeting. James Jackson. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2360)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1901)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2018)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2017)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 39, Cassette 2013)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 6, Dec 15, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1863)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 8, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1923)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 9, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1920)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 11, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1895)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, Report, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 40, Cassette 2361)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, Report, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 36, Cassette 1099)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, Report, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 36, Cassette 1113)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston. Tape 1, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1861)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston. Tape 2, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 45, Cassette 1881)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 42, Cassette 2744)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2696)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2698)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 3, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2697)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jun 1, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1924)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 4, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1925)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 6, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1862)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7, Jun 1, 1985-Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1858)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 8, Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1859)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 9, Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1860)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 10, Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1919)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 11, Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1898)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 12, Jun 2, 1985 (Box 45, Cassette 1899)
    - [Central Committee (?) Meeting]. Gus Hall, Report (draft). Tape 1, Dec 10, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2740)
    - [Central Committee (?) Meeting]. Gus Hall, Report. Tape 1, Dec 10, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2742)
    - [Central Committee (?) Meeting]. Gus Hall, Report on Summit and AFL-CIO Convention. Tape 2, Dec 10, 1985 (Box 42, Cassette 2741)
    - Central Committee Meeting. James Jackson, on The Color Purple, Jan 10, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2365)
    - Central Committee / National Council Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 39, Cassette 2037)
    - Central Committee / National Council Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 39, Cassette 2034)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 42, Cassette 2689)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1892)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1926)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 42, Cassette 2688)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Side A. Tape 2, Side A.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2366)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Side B. Tape 2, Side B.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2367)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 2 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1880)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Side A. Tape 4, Side A.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2368)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Side B. Tape 4, Side B.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2369)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 4 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1911)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1912)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Side A. Tape 6, Side A.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2370)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Side B. Tape 6, Side B *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2371)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 6 *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1910)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7, Side A. Tape 8, Side A.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2372)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7, Side B. Tape 8, Side B *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2373)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 9, Side A. Tape 10, Side A.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2374)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 9, Side B. Tape 10, Side B *, Jan 18, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2375)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 10 *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1913)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 11 *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1914)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary. Tape 12 *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1915)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 13, Side A. Tape 14, Side A *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2376)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 13, Side B. Tape 14, Side B *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2377)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 15, Side A. Tape 16, Side A *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2378)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 15, Side B. Tape 16, Side B *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2379)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1905)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 39, Cassette 2035)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 36, Cassette 1070)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1916)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 40, Cassette 2380)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, on Art Shields. Jim West. Tape 9.* [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1890)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston, on Art and Esther Shields. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu] *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 36, Cassette 979)
    - Central Committee Meeting. James Jackson, on The Color Purple*, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 39, Cassette 2036)
    - Central Committee Meeting. James Jackson, on The Color Purple, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 49, Cassette 3574)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7 *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1865)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 8 *, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 45, Cassette 1864)
    - [Central Committee (?) Meeting], [1987 (?)] (Box 44, Cassette 2641)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Main Report, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 42, Cassette 2690)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Special Presentation, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2388)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1 *, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2389)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 2 *, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2390)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3 *, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2391)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 4 *, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2392)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5 *, Mar 7, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2393)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Mar 7, 1987-Mar 9, 1987 (Box 45, Cassette 1868)
    - Central Committee / National [Committee (?)] Meeting. Tape 3 - 4, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 47, Cassette 2192)
    - Central Committee / National [Committee (?)] Meeting. Tape 5 - 6, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 47, Cassette 2191)
    - Central Committee / National [Committee (?)] Meeting. Tape 7 - 8, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 47, Cassette 2190)
    - Central Committee / National [Committee (?)] Meeting. Tape 9, Side A, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 47, Cassette 2189)
    - Central Committee / National [Committee (?)] Meeting. Tape 9, Side B, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 47, Cassette 2188)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Introduction, May 28, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2394)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Chicago, IL. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 1, Aug 14, 1987 (Box 42, Cassette 2693)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Chicago, IL. Gus Hall, Main Report. Tape 2, Aug 14, 1987 (Box 42, Cassette 2692)
    - Central Committee / National Committee Meetings. West Coast Delagates. Tape 1 *, Oct 24, 1987; Apr 23, 1988; Jan 28, 1989; Jan 27, 1990; Aug 4, 1990; Jan 25, 1991; May 18, 1991; Nov 16, 1991 (Box 30, Cassette 1505)
    - Central Committee / National Committee Meetings. West Coast Delagates. Tape 2 *, Oct 24, 1987; Apr 23, 1988; Jan 28, 1989; Jan 27, 1990; Aug 4, 1990; Jan 25, 1991; May 18, 1991; Nov 16, 1991 (Box 30, Cassette 1506)
    - Central Committee / National Committee Meetings. West Coast Delegates. Tape 3, Oct 24, 1987; Apr 23, 1988; Jan 28, 1989; Jan 27, 1990; Aug 4, 1990; Jan 25, 1991; May 18, 1991; Nov 16, 1991 (Box 30, Cassette 1574)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 1, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 42, Cassette 2703)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Side A. Tape 2, Side A *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2395)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Side B. Tape 2, Side B *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2396)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Side A. Tape 4, Side A *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2397)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Side B. Tape 4, Side B *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2398)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Side A. Tape 6, Side A *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2399)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Side B. Tape 6, Side B *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2400)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7, Side A. Tape 8, Side A *, Oct 24, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2401)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Sid Taylor, Oct 25, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2402)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Gus Hall, Summary, Oct 25, 1987 (Box 40, Cassette 2403)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 1, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2406)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 2, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2407)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 3, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2408)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 4, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2409)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 5, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2410)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 6, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2411)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 7, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2412)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 8, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2413)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 9, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2414)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 10, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2415)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 11, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2416)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 12, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2417)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 13, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2418)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 14, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2419)
    - Central Committee / National Council / National Committee Meeting. Tape 15, Apr 23, 1988-Apr 25, 1988 (Box 40, Cassette 2420)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Report on Conference in New York, NY. Tape 7, Jun 30 (Box 36, Cassette 1087)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Henry Winston. Tape 2, Dec 16 (Box 40, Cassette 2364)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Report on Chicanos. Tape 2, Dec 18 (Box 34, Cassette 1685)
    - Central Committee Meeting, [Dec 18] (Box 34, Cassette 1686)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], [Dec 18] (Box 34, Cassette 1684)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, [Dec 18] (Box 34, Cassette 1682)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 6, Dec 19 (Box 34, Cassette 1688)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 7, [Dec 19] (Box 34, Cassette 1687)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 8, Dec 19 (Box 34, Cassette 1689)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Discussion. Tape 5, undated (Box 34, Cassette 1606)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Messge from the Communist Party of Great Britian, undated (Box 40, Cassette 2421)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, undated (Box 45, Cassette 1937)
    - Central Committee Meeting. Tape 5, undated (Box 39, Cassette 2009)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Report on 1976 Elections. Tape 1, Feb 17, 1976 (Box 28, Cassette 1226)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Report on 1976 Election Campaign, Feb 19, 1976 (Box 42, Cassette 2749)
    - [Political Bureau (?) Meeting]. Henry Winston, Report on Visit to Soviet Union and Vietnam, Feb 15, 1977 (Box 36, Cassette 1067)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Discussing Aims and Youth. Includes Gus Hall, Apr 6, 1977 (Box 30, Cassette 1525)
    - Political Bureau Meeting, Aug 9, 1977 (Box 39, Cassette 2007)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Opening Report. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Mar 7, 1978 (Box 45, Cassette 1936)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Henry Winston, Sep 27, 1978 (Box 33, Cassette 2462)
    - Political Bureau Meeting, Nov 21, 1978 (Box 33, Cassette 2463)
    - Political Bureau Meeting, Nov 21, 1978 (Box 33, Cassette 2464)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Henry Winston, Black Liberation. Tape 2, Nov 21, 1978 (Box 33, Cassette 2465)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Black Liberation Resolution. Includes James Jackson, Charlene Mitchell, Helen (?), Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner. Tape 1, Feb 27, 1979 (Box 35, Cassette 3019)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Black Liberation Resolution, Discussion. Includes Jarvis Tyner, Betty Smith, Bill T., Henry Winston, Tommy (?) and Carl Winters. Tape 2, Feb 27, 1979 (Box 35, Cassette 3020)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Black Liberation Resolution, Summary and Motions. Includes Ted Bassett, Lou Diskin, James Jackson. Tape 3, Feb 27, 1979 (Box 35, Cassette 3021)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Includes Henry Winston, Jarvis Tyner, Ted [Bassett], James Steele, Charlene [Mitchell], Antar [Mberi], Carl [Winter]. Tape 1, Nov 6, 1979 (Box 59, Cassette 1053)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gil Green, Re-industrialization, Aug 26, 1980 (Box 33, Cassette 2466)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. George Meyers and Henry Winston, Dec 9, 1980 (Box 33, Cassette 2467)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Henry Winston, Report on Party Building. Tape 1, Jan 6, 1981 (Box 33, Cassette 2468)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Henry Winston, Report on Party Building. Tape 2, Jan 6, 1981 (Box 33, Cassette 2469)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Report on National School and Writers' Conference. Tape 3. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Nov 10, 1981 (Box 33, Cassette 2470)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Includes Gus Hall, T. Dennis, Henry Winston on Affirmative Action. Tape 1, Jan 4, 1982 (Box 30, Cassette 1565)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Includes Henry Winston, Gus Hall, Charlene Mitchell. Tape 2, Jan 4, 1982 (Box 30, Cassette 1564)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Includes [Roscoe (?)] Proctor, James Jackson, John Pittman, Gus Hall. Tape 3, Jan 4, 1982 (Box 30, Cassette 1563)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Mar 4, 1982-[Mar 5, 1982] (Box 33, Cassette 2471)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Report on Trip, Sep 1, 1982 (Box 33, Cassette 2473)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Si Gerson. Report on New York Elections, Sep 28, 1982 (Box 45, Cassette 1876)
    - Political Bureau (?) Meeting. Gus Hall Birthday Celebration, Oct 12, 1982 (Box 51, Cassette 3267)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Nov 12, 1982 (Box 33, Cassette 2474)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 1, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 44, Cassette 2674)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 2, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 44, Cassette 2676)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 3, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 44, Cassette 2677)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall. Tape 4, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 44, Cassette 2678)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, James Jackson and Henry Winston, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 33, Cassette 2472)
    - Political Bureau Meeting. Gus Hall, Presentation, Dec 8, 1982 (Box 33, Cassette 2475)